"♪Don't stay trapped inside your room♪
♪Outside the window,
the rain has cleared♪
♪Set reality aside♪
♪Follow your heart♪
♪What you've been longing
for is right ahead♪
♪Don't act like you didn't see it♪
♪Just be a little braver♪
♪Come closer, come closer♪
♪There's a little spark
shining in your eyes♪
♪That's the signal
of a heart coming alive♪
of a heart coming alive♪"
=Heart Signal (China Version) S9=
(Bonus Edition)
(Yu Yang returns to Signal House)
Hello.
Hi, Yu Yang.
Happy Children's Day!
Happy Children's Day, Yu Yang!
Yu Yang, did you bring any food?
I did.
We all brought a ton of food.
I really did.
What did you bring?
I just brought some stuff
we can eat right away.
Nice.
- Good.
- Yeah.
All right, let's plate everything.
It's like New Year's today.
Okay.
Let's get this out carefully.
(Unpacking the cake)
I think it probably fell apart.
How do we open this?
(Asking)
You open it.
I don't know either.
How do we open it?
We should peel this off, right?
Yeah.
Let's see.
Not bad.
A little messed up.
Let's fix it.
Sure.
This part here.
It's fine.
We just need to move it to the top.
I'll go get a tool.
Yeah.
Do we have a fork?
I don't know.
Maybe we should get two tools.
Oh no, it's falling apart.
It's okay.
How about a spoon?
Sure.
Let's put it on first.
Then we'll spread it out.
Like this.
I'll hold this side up.
Can you tell what shape it is?
(Thinking)
It should be...
A cloud.
I thought it was a little animal.
And then its head fell off.
(Amused)
Slowly, lift it up.
Looks pretty good.
My hands are shaking so much.
(Amused)
Not bad.
Good.
Nice.
This actually looks pretty nice.
Yeah.
You can eat the apple for me.
Okay, I'll eat the apple for you.
There's more apple in here.
You want some?
There's more apple?
Yeah.
Should I scoop it out?
Sure.
This apple should be
a little sweet.
Okay.
I'll eat these two first.
Let me try it.
I'll find a fork.
(Laughing)
Si, do you want to try the cooked apple?
What's this?
It's that cooked apple.
Okay, let's go over there.
- We'll eat it together.
- Okay, sure.
We're already using these bowls.
That's right.
Let me try it first.
Is it good?
It's a sweet, beef-flavored apple.
Beef-flavored?
It was cooked in the pot for a while.
(Liang Renfang comes to the dining room)
(Looking)
(Approaching)
Whose is this?
I brought it.
Healthy food.
I can't eat spicy food.
I prefer light meals.
(Memorizing that)
(Smiling)
Okay.
Let's clean this.
Another one.
Maybe we should clean everything
when we're done.
It's okay.
I'll clean some of this first.
Then we'll have less to do later.
Thanks.
Such a thoughtful woman.
I feel like otherwise,
we'll be exhausted later.
(Glances)
That apple really does
taste like beef.
Really.
Of course.
It was cooked for a while.
It's actually pretty good.
It's pretty unusual.
Usually,
I'd eat the apple first
after cooking it.
You would eat the apple first.
Right.
Otherwise, it gets too sweet
if you leave it too long.
Did you make this?
Yeah.
You seem pretty good at cooking.
Who?
Everyone's good at cooking.
Look at that table.
(Turns to look)
What they made is pretty impressive.
They're all pretty
challenging.
Do you have a tissue?
(Notices)
I'll get you one.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
It's a little spicy.
Never mind then.
I think it is a little spicy.
I ate fried chicken yesterday,
and I broke out.
(Glances)
Didn't see anything.
Nope.
(Smiles)
If I can't see it, it's not there.
Okay.
Fang, I feel like Yu Yang
became so much more relaxed
after spending time with you yesterday.
(Smiles)
(Laughs)
From what I've seen these past few days,
Yu Yang has become a completely
different person.
He was relaxed from head to toe.
Even his brain was relaxed.
Who's your roommate?
My roommate?
(Points)
(Imitates)
What?
What do you mean?
Our secret code.
(Laughs)
Secret code.
That's some serious secret code.
(Laughs)
Let's start washing dishes.
Okay.
(Cleaning up after the meal)
You pick up the chopsticks.
I'll wash the bowls.
Okay.
We're heading out first.
Okay, we'll wash them.
Bye bye.
Bye.
Is it easy to wash them over there?
Why don't you come over here?
(Switches places)
Neither of us is wearing an apron.
Go put one on.
You can wash the dishes.
And I'll wipe the plates.
Okay.
There's some of your flour on this.
Flour.
Flour? That's the one I just wore.
I can't get my hands through it, so...
Then how do you wear it?
Just put it around my neck.
Then let's do it like this.
Let's do it like this.
Like this.
Yeah, I can't get my hands through.
(Laughs)
This is the only way.
That works too.
You seem trapped in there.
Your hands really can't get out?
It's fine.
As long as I can wash.
Then I'll wipe them.
Okay.
Feels like I'm tied up.
(Glances)
I can only wash dishes like this now.
I can't stretch my arms out either.
Come on, you two. Pick two.
You're the first ones to get them.
I'll pick two.
Sure.
Let's go with this one.
Take it out.
Is this a tulip?
Yeah.
Okay.
There should be a stem
or something underneath.
I'll get it out for you.
You do it. I'm afraid I'll break it.
It's fine. It won't hurt it.
There.
There should be something
for arranging it.
I literally just ripped it apart.
Beautiful.
Let me see if there's a bigger one.
It's fine. These two are enough.
Let's take this one too.
Okay.
You can put them together.
I'll put them here.
Okay.
We'll take them with us later.
Thanks, Meng.
It's for you.
Thank you.
One for each of you.
This one.
Soak it in water for a while.
Then we can take them
and keep them in our room.
Okay.
Si.
Here's one for you.
Pick one.
Thank you.
It's orange.
So pretty.
I remember you said
that you liked tulips.
So I thought about it.
Then I thought,
let's get tulips.
Then I have to keep this alive.
You can pull off these leaves.
So they won't take up the water.
Just cut the stem
at an angle and put it in.
It smells nice.
Yeah.
Just a little.
Yeah, it smells pretty good
So pretty.
You look beautiful with this flower.
(Praises)
Thank you.
We should take a photo together here.
Let's...
Wait.
Where's my camera?
Let's take some photos.
Sure.
Wait a second.
(Takes out camera)
Come on, Si.
Let me take a beautiful photo
of you.
Good. You look Korean.
So pretty.
Very retro.
They're almost done washing the dishes.
Let's take a picture of them.
Let's go take a look.
We'll take one
while they're washing the dishes.
Let's get a picture of you two.
Do you want to take a picture together
wearing these aprons?
Sure.
Cao Yiheng looks really natural now.
Do I need to put my arms through?
Yeah, it'll look better.
It'll look better.
Right. Get ready first.
Here, take a spoon.
Three, two, one.
Looks good.
These gloves match perfectly.
Good thing we remembered to put them on.
Good thing you did. Seriously.
I put your photo right here.
Okay, we'll get them later.
Thanks, Meng.
Enjoy washing the dishes.
Thanks.
It looks so good.
We won't bother you anymore.
Bye bye.
Okay, we got a great photo.
Now we're all fired up to do our chores.
Back to reality.
Yeah, back to reality.
Back to washing dishes.
Back to reality.
(Live audience)
Watching someone play the piano
really does calm you down.
Yeah.
It puts you in a daze.
You don't want
to think about anything
related to the "stars".
The "stars" just drift
through the universe.
It really does calm you down.
Yeah.
Let's just be the audience.
Okay.
(Glances)
I'm thinking I should find a good time
to call them over for a group photo.
You probably wouldn't just go up to them
and ask if they want
to take a photo, right?
I could.
You could?
So you're not what I thought.
Then I'll go get Xilun.
Don't.
I'll ask them if they want to.
I'll ask him to take a photo together.
Don't.
That's terrifying.
It's honestly hilarious.
We can wait for them to come over later.
They might want some time to talk.
Do you guys want to take a photo?
Sure.
Liaing Xiaoyu, do you want a photo?
Sure, no problem.
This spot looks so good.
Seriously, this spot is beautiful.
Why don't you move a little closer
to that round window?
Yeah.
Three, two, one.
Let's take a look.
That circle.
Nice.
The composition is great.
This really looks good.
I want one here too.
Come on.
I'll take one for you.
I think this spot looks really good.
(Glances)
That's hilarious.
Let me take one of you two first.
Sure.
Move a little closer.
(Helping out)
Okay.
(Come closer)
Xilun, smile.
One,
two.
No fake smiles.
Handsome guy and beautiful girl.
Hope it looks good.
It's good.
This one really looks good.
Looks good.
Even your smile looks good.
(Take a look)
You look so natural in this one.
This one looks great.
(Smiles)
Turn around.
Okay, turn around.
It's floating over here.
Let it drift for a bit.
Look at that water droplet.
That's amazing.
Can you make anything
with lotus leaves?
Lotus leaf-wrapped chicken.
It's really good.
Okay.
Can you make it?
I can learn.
(Laughs)
Do you usually cook
for yourself at home?
Yeah.
What have you made
that you think tastes really good?
I feel like
I can make pretty much anything.
I just look at the recipe.
I can make a little of anything
by following a recipe.
Me too.
I especially like making breakfast.
So
when you're at home,
you usually make breakfast yourself?
Custard buns.
Siu mai and stuff.
Yeah, and eggs.
One for me,
and one for my dog.
Your dog?
You have to make breakfast
for your dog too?
Yeah, I make it for him.
What does he eat?
Chicken breast and stuff.
Then I add blueberries.
He eats pretty well then.
Egg yolks.
Yeah.
Sometimes I also give him
freeze-dried salmon and stuff.
He eats really well.
Happy little dog.
That's a huge mosquito bite.
It's really big.
Let me spray
some mosquito repellent on it.
Maybe that'll help.
(Care for her)
Stop the itching.
It should help with the itching, right?
Thanks.
Okay.
I think your arm
could use a little more.
Make it more concentrated.
Thanks.
So when you all
go out to perform together,
do you guys hang out together?
Yeah.
I feel like
people
who study musical theater
are really fun.
What do you mean?
I feel like musical theater means
you have to know how to sing and dance.
(Happy)
I played The Little Mermaid recently.
That suits you.
Wasn't that basically playing yourself?
What do you mean?
The Little Mermaid.
I just feel like you're perfect
for the role.
Thanks.
If I get the chance,
I'll go see it.
Okay.
I really want
to watch you guys rehearse.
Okay.
Stargazing room.
If we row around here
and look at the stars...
There are stars.
Look.
You can point at the stars, right?
Yeah, you can.
Do you think they are still there?
They should be.
They can't have eaten that fast, right?
Who goes there just to eat?
Go there just to eat.
Yeah.
Liang Renfang and Yu Yang.
Who's that?
Hi.
So romantic.
You know, we were just talking
about how no one
would probably be out rowing
this late at night.
Then we turned around and saw you two.
We're just floating around here.
We're the Courageous.
Yeah, you are.
You're extremely brave.
The moon is really full tonight.
You can take a look.
Really?
Where?
You two enjoy.
We'll leave you two alone for now.
We're going to adjust this telescope.
Okay.
There are stars.
Get it adjusted so you can see them.
(Everyone gradually heads out)
(Knock, knock, knock)
Hello.
Hi.
(Smiles)
You got up early again today.
You...
What are you doing?
I was thinking of making breakfast.
You haven't eaten yet, have you?
(Asks proactively)
No.
Okay, I'll make you something.
Okay, thanks.
No problem. Just wait over there.
Okay.
What made you decide
(Asking)
to come down for breakfast?
I got up pretty early today,
so I had a little extra time.
It's okay. No rush.
(Sneaks a glance)
(Glances)
(Another glance)
(Asking)
What can I do?
Wash these.
(Hands over blueberries)
Okay.
We can eat them later.
Have you had this before?
(Chili powder)
Here.
(Freshly washed blueberries)
Thanks.
Chili flakes.
You eat chili flakes for breakfast?
No.
You can have them with bread.
I didn't know if you'd eat this.
You can add some.
You...
You don't like this?
You don't like it?
I've never had it.
You can try it in a bit.
I'll put some on the side.
You can try it later.
Let's give it a taste.
I'll put it here.
Okay, thanks.
You can try it first.
Try this.
(Repeats)
See if you like the flavor.
What?
I said, try this.
See if you like it.
Okay, sure.
I dip it in, right?
Okay.
Is it good?
So that's what it tastes like.
That's so interesting.
There's eggs here.
You should have some eggs too.
(Again)
Have some eggs.
Okay, sure.
(Both laugh)
I feel like neither of us
can really hear each other when we talk.
I...
I'll speak a little louder then.
(I'll speak a little louder)
Thanks.
It's pretty good.
Let's go.
(Don't go anywhere. The next episode
is even more romantic)